gojiyo.com 2010-10-29

# Find Friends | Send Messages | Create your Profile - Gojiyo.com

### Privacy policy

At GoJiyo, we are committed to protecting your privacy and creating a strong bond with our customers. This privacy policy explains the use of information collected via our website, customer service operations and GoJiyo service. As used in this privacy policy, the term 'personal information' means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home.

#### Do read this information carefully

  1. We collect personal information and usage statistics to maintain a high-quality customer experience and deliver superior customer service.
  2. Some information we request directly from you during registration. Other pieces of data are gathered indirectly from website traffic, your computer hardware and Internet connection, or GoJiyo usage. This information is purely technical information. 
  3. GoJiyo does not disclose personal information you provide it to any third parties without your permission. Whenever information will be shared it is explicitly mentioned at the time of collecting the said information. 

GoJiyo may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GoJiyo, this web site or any user of GoJiyo;

(b) protect and defend the rights or property of GoJiyo, Godrej or the users of GoJiyo; or

(c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of this web site, GoJiyo or the public.

In addition, if GoJiyo should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may transfer the information you provide to us on this site to the company with whom we merge after intimating the same to you.

  4. You will have the ability to update the personal data you provided to us during registration by contacting us at <http://gojiyo.com/support>.
  5. We will update this privacy policy in a timely fashion when any changes occur

#### The privacy policy below refers to the online service GoJiyo and the following website: http://gojiyo.com.

#### The Information We Collect and How We Collect It

There are different levels of information we collect, depending upon your relationship to GoJiyo and Godrej.

Anonymous Website Visitor: If you visit our websites we automatically record information related to your IP address, GoJiyo cookie information, and aggregate information on what content you access or visit. This information is collected in the background while you move around our website.

Mailing List Member: If you choose to provide us personal information in order to subscribe to our mailing list, we collect information to aid delivery and preferences such as e-mail address and message performance statistics.

Registered Website Member: If you choose to register on our website, we will track broad site usage information as well as aggregate usage of website community features such as downloads and forums. This is in addition to the personal data collected during the registration process. 

GoJiyo User: If you install or use the GoJiyo software, we collect and aggregate a variety of data to monitor system and simulation performance, and to verify your unique identity. This includes specific and general information about your computer hardware and Internet connection, which are stored together but are not personally identifiable. We track usage of customer-service resources in order to ensure high quality interactions. This is in addition to the personal data and billing information collected during the registration process.

Additionally there are a few special situations to note:

    * Service Beta User: If you volunteer to serve as a beta user for pre-commercial content, we will track bug reports and potentially individual system performance in an effort to rigorously test pre-deployed technology.
    * Former Customer: If you cease being a customer of ours, we will keep a copy of your registration file in our database for use in the event you wish to rejoin the GoJiyo service.
    * Response to Job Postings or Unsolicited Communications: Please note that information we receive in reference to a job posting or via unsolicited communications does not fall under the privacy terms outlined in this policy. However, information from your resume will be used solely for the purposes of evaluating your candidacy for employment.
    * Individuals Outside of the India: Anyone using the GoJiyo website from outside of India should be aware that personal Information collected on these websites may be stored and processed in India or any other country in which GoJiyo or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using these websites, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

#### Information Displayed to Other Users

Information about your account is displayed to other users in your GoJiyo profile, and this same information may be available through automated script calls and application program interfaces. This information includes your account name, account type, the date your account was established, whether or not you are currently online, user rating information, group and partner information, and whether or not you have established a payment account or transaction history with GoJiyo. However, we will not display your actual name, address, or credit card or bank account numbers, except with your express permission or as otherwise permitted by this privacy policy and our terms of service.

#### Disclosing Personal Information in Profiles, Forums or within GoJiyo

You may choose to disclose personal information in our online forums, via your GoJiyo profile, directly to other users in chat or otherwise while using the GoJiyo service. Please be aware that such information is public information and you should not expect privacy or confidentiality in these settings.

#### How We Protect Your Personal Data

We comply with applicable laws and industry standards when transferring, receiving and storing consumer data. Access to your personal information is limited to those GoJiyo employees who require the information in order to provide products or services to you or perform their jobs.

#### Notice to Those Under the Age of 18

Only individuals who are 18 years of age or older are permitted to register. Registration for our mailing list, website and/or GoJiyo service requires entry of a valid and eligible Date of Birth.

#### Your Consent

Periodically we may need to update our privacy policy to reflect changes in the types of information we collect, the means we use to collect information, and/or our usage of collected information. When this occurs we will make reasonable efforts to alert you to these changes. Your use of the GoJiyo website and/or any GoJiyo products or services (including without limitation GoJiyo) noted above signifies your assent to this GoJiyo Privacy Policy.
